see.me 2016-02-01

# See | Me - Bringing creativity back to the real world.

## PRIVACY POLICY

Thank you for visiting our website at www.See.Me (the “site”). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at See.Me. By using any portion of our site, including, without limitation, submitting your artwork to our site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement (the “policy”) as they may be amended from time to time. As we update and expand our services, this policy may change, so we encourage you to visit this page periodically. Continued access of this site by you will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the policy. If you cannot agree with the terms and conditions of this policy, please do not use our site. Please also note that this policy does not address our practices regarding information that we collect through any website, or by any other means, other than through this site.

### Collected Information

The information we collect is gathered from several sources. These include, without limitation, our e-Newsletter subscription forms, site registration, online galleries, contest entries, website message postings, survey information and purchases via telephone, direct mail, email and other electronic sources. From these sources, we may collect postal addresses, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address), and/or demographic information for those individuals who volunteer such information. When you visit our site, our web server automatically recognizes the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the website that referred you, and the Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, but no other identifiable information unless volunteered. In addition, we collect aggregate information on what web pages visitors access. We use this information for purposes such as calculating site usage levels, helping diagnose problems with the site’s servers, administering the site, and improving site-related services and features.

### How We Use Collected Information

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our web pages, customize the content and layout of our pages for each individual visitor, and/or notify visitors about updates to our site. As part of a subscription, gallery usage, registration, or contest entry agreement, subscribers, contest entrants, and registrants (galleries and other registrants) can be contacted by us through both mail and e-mail to communicate with them about their subscription, registration, contests, and topics that may be of interest. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers online will only receive telephone contact from us with information regarding orders they have placed online or any contest entry. We also may use the information to contact them for marketing purposes.

We work with third parties who provide services including, but not limited to, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment and other services of an administrative nature. We reserve the right to share information about you with such third parties for the purpose of enabling them to provide these services. For example, if you choose to make a purchase through the site, we may share your payment information or other information with our third party service providers to fulfill your purchase, including, without limitation, to process your credit card or payment account number or to ship products to you.

Notwithstanding any other provision of this policy to the contrary, we reserve the right to disclose information about you to others as we believe to be appropriate (a) under applicable law; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to governmental requests; (d) to enforce our Terms of Use; (e) to protect our operations; (f) to protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of our company, you, or others; and (g) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain. For example, we may, to the fullest extent the law allows, disclose information about you to law enforcement agencies to assist them in identifying individuals who have been or may be engaged in unlawful activities.

We reserve the right to transfer any and all information that we collect from the site users to a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or ownership interests (including, without limitation, in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

In an effort to give See.Me members more opportunities for promotion and recognition, we will from time to time post members' work to our social media channels, including, but not limited to, Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, and Tumblr. When images are posted to any of those sites, those images become subject to the privacy policies and terms of use of those sites, which are not under the control of See.Me.

### Postal Communications

If you supply us with your postal address online, you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by writing to us at the below address. 

### E-mail Communications

If you have registered for our products and/or services, entered a contest and/or have supplied an e-mail address, you will receive emails pertaining to these types of products, services and upcoming contests. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by clicking unsubscribe at the bottom of any our e-mails.

From time to time, we make the e-mail addresses of those who opt in and sign up for our e-Newsletters and contest promotions available to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your e-mail address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by clicking unsubscribe at the bottom of all our e-mails.

See.Me (“See.Me”) sometimes may offer contests, sweepstakes or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with identified third parties. By virtue of their sponsorship, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. See.Me has no control over the third-party sponsors’ use of this information.

### Attention, Kids

If you are under the age of 18 but are at least 13 years old, you may submit information about yourself to the site only if authorized to do so by a parent or legal guardian.

If you are under the age of 13 (12 or younger), you may not provide any information about yourself to the site. While you may view content on the site, you may not register with the site, enter any of our sweepstakes or contests or participate in any of our chat rooms, bulletin boards, or other activities that would let you enter information about yourself. If we learn that you have provided information about yourself to the site, we will delete such information.

### Note to Parents

See.Me will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from kids under 13 or from minors under 18 who are not authorized by a parent or legal guardian. If you have any concerns about the site or its related services, wish to find out if your child is a member of one of our services, or wish to cancel your child's membership, please contact us at [hello@see.me](mailto:hello@see.me)

### Ad Servers

To bring you offers that may be of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address, and click-stream information.

See.Me may use reputable third parties to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its web pages and to conduct research about the advertisements. Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that such third parties may have collected from you or the methods used by the third parties to collect that information (e.g., cookies, web beacons, and clear GIFs).

PLEASE NOTE THAT THIS POLICY DOES NOT ADDRESS THE PRIVACY OR INFORMATION PRACTICES OF ANY THIRD PARTIES.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in this policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our site periodically. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by following the information above. Upon request, we provide site visitors with access to information we maintain about them, unique identifier information (e.g., customer number or password) that we maintain about them, transaction information (e.g., dates on which customers made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) that we maintain about them, communications that the consumer/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries), and contact information (e.g., name, address, phone number) that we maintain about them.

Consumers can access this information by signing into the customer service area of our site.

In reference to customer subscriptions, upon request, we offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information. Consumers can have all other, non-subscription information corrected by e-mailing or writing to us at the below address.

### Security

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site, and when we transfer and receive financial information, transactions are conducted through a secure server.

Access to this information is available to you through a unique username and password. The password is encrypted and we recommend that you not divulge it to anyone. In addition, your registration information resides on a secure server that only selected See.Me personnel have access to. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or data storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, although we strive to protect personal information you provide to us, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us through or in connection with the site or that is stored by us. You acknowledge and agree that any information you transmit through the site or upload for storage in connection with the site is so transmitted or stored at your own risk. When you order products or services through the site, you will create a unique username and password. As stated above, we recommend that you not divulge the password to anyone. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), you must immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us at the address or email address listed below (note that if you choose to notify us via physical mail, this will delay the time it takes for us to respond to the problem). If you would like to update any personal information that you have previously provided to us through the site, you may do so by contacting us at [hello@see.me](mailto:hello@see.me).

IMPORTANT : DO NOT DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION IN FORUMS OR ON MESSAGE BOARDS. WHENEVER YOU DO SO, ALL OF THAT INFORMATION CAN BE COLLECTED AND USED BY OTHERS. IF YOU POST PERSONAL INFORMATION IN PUBLIC PLACES, OTHERS MAY SEND YOU UNSOLICITED E-MAIL MESSAGES. BE CAREFUL AND SMART WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.

If you feel that we have not complied with the policy, you may contact us at the below address.

Our postal address is:

26-19 Jackson Ave, Long Island City, NY 11101

We can also be reached via e-mail at [hello@see.me](mailto:hello@see.me).
